<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<layer-list xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
    <item>
        <shape xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
            android:shape="oval">

            <solid android:color="@android:color/holo_blue_light" />
<padding
    android:top="4sp"
    android:bottom="4sp"
    android:left="4sp"
    android:right="4sp"/>
        </shape>
        Notes App mobile notes app notes ios app design ios designer dark mode dark ui dark app ux mobile ui app design ux design ui exploration ui design design shots
        Notes App
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        0
        20
        Farmers App farmers market purple farm farmer ux mobile ui app design ux design ui design ui design shots
        Farmers App
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        0
        8
        Farmer Apps farmers market farm app app design mobile ui ux ux design ui design ui exploration design shots
        Farmer Apps
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        2
        7
        Wireframe - Farmer Apps app design wireframe ux mobile ui ux design ui ui design exploration design shots
        1
        Wireframe - Farmer Apps
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        0
        4
        Covid19 Landing Page web website covid19 girl red virus web design landing page ui design ui design shots
        Covid19 Landing Page
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        4
        12
        Food chocolate milk donut shading food vector illustration exploration design shots
        Food
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        0
        8
        Teamwork design exploration vector teamwork team character illustration shots
        Teamwork
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        2
        17
        Healthcare Landing Page Concept designer ux design exploration healthcare doctor blue website landing page ui design ui illustration design shots
        Healthcare Landing Page Concept
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        0
        20
        Home Decoration Website Concept landing page homepage website ui  ux ux design ui design green decoration web design design shots
        Home Decoration Website Concept
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        0
        15
        Angkot - Public Transsportation App Concept Design user interface indonesia transsportation case study uiux ux design ui design ux mobile ui ios design ui app design shots
        Angkot - Public Transsportation App Concept Design
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        2
        27
        Flowers Shop Exploration mobile ui exploration app design ios app plants flowers design ui shots
        Flowers Shop Exploration
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        0
        16
        Hello Dribbble ! pink hello dribbble debut shots first
        Hello Dribbble !
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Reynaldi Daniel
        13
        125
        Dribbble is the world’s leading community for creatives to share, grow, and get hired.

        For designers
        Go Pro!
        Explore design work
        Design blog
        Overtime podcast
        Dribbble meetups
        Playoffs
        Weekly Warm-Up
        Code of conduct
        Hire designers
        Post a job opening
        Post a freelance project
        Search for designers
        Brands
        Advertise with us
        Company
        About
        Careers
        Support
        Media kit
        Dribbble shop
        Testimonials
        API
        Terms of service
        Privacy policy
        Directories
        Top designers
        Top design teams
        Design jobs
        Tags
        Places
        Design assets
        Shop Creative Market
        ads via Carbon
        Elevate your portfolio with millions of unique, ready-to-use design assets
        ADVERTISE ON DRIBBBLE
        © 2020 Dribbble. All rights reserved.
        Made with ♥ remotely from
        Worcester, MADenver, COMontreal, QuebecOrlando, FLRoseville, MNSilver Spring, MDMinneapolis, MNLos Angeles, CACanadaOttawa, OntarioMontrealNorth Vancouver, BCGrass Valley, CaliforniaVictoria, BCAustin, TXCavite, PhilippinesVictoriaVancouver, BCMontreal, CanadaToronto, ONAtlantaSan Diego, CAEverywhereSidney, BC
        14,007,870 shots dribbbled
        Dribbble ball iconIcon shot x light
        Icon shot next light

        Get a domain and create a website with Squaresspace.
        Don't want to see ads? Go Pro!
        Start a Free Trial
        Advertisement
        Reynaldi Daniel
        Notes App
        by Reynaldi Daniel
        Save  Like
        Hello👋
        Today i want to share my design exploration about notes app. Well, beside the light theme, i also create the dark one. Hope you like it, don't forget to give like and feedbacks🤩
        Thankyou!

        Pin
        Tweet
        Copy
        app app design dark dark mode dark ui design designer exploration ios ios app design mobile mobile ui notes notes app shots ui ui design ux ux design
        #0C0C0C#DCDCDC#ABABAA#5F574F#FC8810#D75F0F#F4B350#2F36CE
        20 likes
        9 saves
        Apr 22, 2020
        More from Reynaldi Daniel
        Farmers App farmers market purple farm farmer ux mobile ui app design ux design ui design ui design shots
        Farmer Apps farmers market farm app app design mobile ui ux ux design ui design ui exploration design shots
        Wireframe - Farmer Apps app design wireframe ux mobile ui ux design ui ui design exploration design shots
        Covid19 Landing Page web website covid19 girl red virus web design landing page ui design ui design shots
        keyboard shortcuts: ← previous shot → next shot Esc close L or F like

        Notes App
        by Reynaldi Daniel
        96dd6fa4ecbc76242c5e99b654214548

    </item>
    <item android:drawable="@drawable/baseline_star_half_white_24" />
</layer-list>